[Unsoiled Starlight]
[Episode 10]
[Adapted from Migu's novel
"Unsoiled Starlight"]
[Original Writer: Shan Gu Jun]
Here you go.
Enjoy your meal.
You two were
in the Qining High School, right?
Yes.
It's you!
No wonder.
If I had known it was you,
I would have given this young lady
an extra fried egg.
What do you mean?
Young lady, you didn't know?
When you used to come here
to eat by yourself,
this young man
would always secretly follow behind you.
He wouldn't say anything,
just stand over there
and watch you.
Then he would give me money
to add an extra fried egg for you.
It's so nice
that you young people are together.
Are you married?
Not yet.
It'll be soon.
So you were the one
who added that fried egg for me.
I always thought
everyone had two in their bowls.
Well,
I'm sorry.
Why the sudden apology?
Is it because of this?
Not just because of this.
I lost my temper with you that night.
At that time,
some bad things occured
and I couldn't control my emotions.
So,
I took it out on you.
Ms. Shu Tinglan,
I formally accept your apology.
This gesture
and this look...
Every time you make them in a meeting,
we know we're going to get scolded.
Maybe you should do that less from now on.
Although
something dangerous happened,
I finally made it back to Qining,
cheering me up a lot.
You're not even from Qining.
You just went to high school here
for three years.
Was it really that great?
Those three years
mean a lot
to me.
Okay.
You nod, but did you even understand?
Yes.
Heartless.
Shu Tinglan,
can I pursue you?
I was just thinking,
if only in high school
I had the courage
to sit here
and confess my feelings to you.
During those three years,
every time I came to this noodle shop,
I wanted to sit here
and say this to you.
Is it too late for me to say it now?
It's okay.
You don't have to answer me right away.
[Zhuoyuan Technology's New Product Launch]
At this launch event,
Zhuoyuan Technology
will launch
a smart system for all life scenarios,
[Zhuoyuan Technology's New Product Launch]
the Lingxi series of products.
[Performance Boost]
[Zhuoyuan Technology's New Product Launch]
[AI Smart Calling + Real-Time Interaction]
We have realized real-time interaction
in AI smart calling.
In this chip system,
[AI Smart Calling + Real-Time Interaction]
[Boundless Vision —
Redefining the Home Visual Experience]
we also defined
"Boundless Vision".
With low-latency gaming mode,
audio-visual sync
and enhanced performance,
we redefine the home visual experience.
Next is the Q&A session,
which will be conducted by me
and CTO Wen Jian
together.
[Boundless Vision —
Redefining the Home Visual Experience]
Hey, Nannan.
Shushu.
I just watched Zhuoyuan Technology's
new product launch.
This man is so charming.
-We have to hurry. The reporter's Q&A is about to begin.
-Did you seize the chance?
Ms. Wen and Mr. Zhuo,
the golden couple of the tech world,
are definitely worth a report.
Yes.
I'll think about it.
It's New Year's Eve again.
I believe everyone is busy preparing for
the New Year's Eve dinner.
So many dishes.
Did you make them, or...?
I bought them from a restaurant.
You know I'm not good at cooking.
It's a pity Mom can't cook now.
Otherwise, how could you possibly
be so skinny.
When you get better,
I'll make you cook for me every day.
Five meals a day,
until you don't want to cook anymore.
Okay.
Eat more.
You eat more, too.
Okay.
The doctor said your condition
is much better.
We'll move back home soon.
Okay.
Mom,
can you see who it is?
My phone is in my pocket.
[Zhuo Yu'an]
Zhuo.
It's a work call.
I'll take it.
You go ahead and eat.
Okay.
Hello?
Are you at home?
No.
I'm at the hospital with my mom.
I guessed so.
I made New Year's Eve dinner.
Can I bring it over?
That would impose too much on you.
It's very far from downtown.
No big deal.
Turn around.
Happy New Year.
Thank you.
I should have gone in to see your mother,
but...
I'll get going then.
OK.
Since you're already here,
come in and have
New Year's Eve dinner with us.
Mom.
Thank you, ma'am.
[Ward 514]
Thank you.
Zhuo,
have some fish.
He doesn't eat fish.
Mom,
here, have some.
You eat, too.
Ma'am,
I'm a bit of a picky eater.
Please don't mind.
Not at all.
Where are you from, Zhuo?
I'm from Beicheng.
Coincidentally,
-Tinglan and I are...
-...in the same company.
He's my client.
Mom, eat more.
Eat more.
Why aren't you with your family
for the New Year?
I...
My parents were abroad when I was young,
so I seldom eat with my family.
Do you have a girlfriend?
Mom!
I'm still waiting for her reply.
Ah.
Tinglan, eat.
After dinner,
you young people go out and have fun.
As for me,
it's time to rest.
Don't worry about me.
Try this.
Thank you.
What are you thanking me for?
Thank you for coming over
to have New Year's Eve dinner with my mom.
She hasn't been
so happy for a long time.
I should be the one
thanking you and your mom.
I haven't had
a New Year's Eve dinner in years.
Let's go.
By your mom's decree,
I'm taking you out to have fun.
Where are we going?
You'll know when we get there.
Your place.
May I hold your hand?
I've never seen you
so polite before.
My bad.
I'm not sure it's a good idea.
I don't live here often.
You can come often if you want.
Can I
hug you?
Are you planning
to ask for my permission
for every move from now on?
No.
It's just that I don't have immunity.
During the New Year holiday,
you can have immunity.
How about I give this house to you?
You can decorate it however you like.
No.
I have my own home.
I still have to work.
I don't have the energy for it.
But it's very close to your workplace.
It would be very convenient
for your commute.
What?
Do you want to keep me as a pet?
Can I?
No.
Tinglan.
May I kiss you?
I've said that
during the New Year holiday,
you have immunity.
You don't need to ask for my permission.
Happy New Year.
Let's go to Huishan to watch the sunrise.